





NARRA VENKATA RAGHU CHARAN

Third-year Computer Science and Engineering student with experience in DevOps processes through a couple of projects. An inquisitive learner, determined individual and a passionate leader with an ambition to succeed and grow in any given environment.

EDUCATION

Gayatri Vidya Parishad College of Engineering (A)

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science and Engineering, 2020 - 2024 CGPA: 9.1

Intermediate Public Examination

Board of Intermediate of Education, Andhra Pradesh, 2020

Percentage: 96.1%

Secondary School Examination

Central Board of Secondary Education, 2018

CGPA: 9.8

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C, C++, Python, Java, R
- Web Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript (Basics), Django.
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux(Ubuntu).
- Soft skills: Leadership Skills, Networking, Problem-solving, Communication.
- Frameworks and Tools: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Google Cloud, AWS, Android Studio, Weka, Hadoop, Spark, VS Code.

EXPERIENCE

Google Developer Student Club GVP - Google Cloud Facilitator

08-09-2022 - Present.

- Conducted Workshops, Training sessions.
- Guided 50+ students in completion of GCCP.

Skills: Cloud Computing, GCP, Leadership skills

Google Developer Groups Visakhapatnam - Core Volunteer

10-10-2022 - Present

- served as Core volunteer by hosting sessions on Cloud Computing and Services provided by Google Cloud.
- Involved in event management of DevFest-2022-Vizag.

Skills: Problem-Solving, Organization of code fests, Event Management.

Google Developer Student Clubs GVP - Devops Lead

03-09-2022-Present

- Held some sessions on DevOps.
- Hosted Hackathons.

Skills: Leadership, Event management.

PROJECTS

- Asynchronous Calculator (Deployment) Dockerized ReactJs, NodeJs based application and deployed it in Google Kubernetes Engine using Google Cloud Platform. GitHub link
- Kovida (ML based WebApp) based on health conditions app gives personalized Insurance prices. Can be used by Insurance Companies. Tech Stack Used: Python, Streamlit. GitHub Link
- Face Detection And Face Recognition detects a face and recognizes it with trained images. Can be applied to the attendance system. Tech Stack Used: OpenCV, Python, HaarCascade Classifier, Deep Face a OSS. GitHub Link

CERTIFICATES & BADGES

- **Google Cloud Career Practitioner**
- **AWS Cloud Foundations**
- Hacker Rank (Python)
- Google Developer Profile(Android with Kotlin)
- 30 Days of Google Cloud

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Writes at @nvrc.hashnode.dev
- Blogging (Reads Articles)
- Sports

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu